this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his captured brother ace
to do so he snuck into the government prison impelled down
luffy has now made his way down to level two known as the wild beast hell along with buggy the clown
that you say someone broke into the prison absurd this is impelled down no one has ever
infiltrated its walls our defenses are flawless how could we possibly allow this have they found this
out transfer the video footage to my chambers warden i was wondering would it be possible to see the
prisoner now sure let's go like right now warden wake up we kind of need you to deal with this
i couldn't help but overhear you if you're having trouble on this floor i can help is that so who are
you long time no sea straw hat luffy you helped me out without noticing how fortunate i am a man who
always pays back his debts i know you wait it's the three hair oh yeah you were on the island with the
giants right three mr three you fool
warlord in prison jimbe the honorable pirate
when i was assigned to this level i was a little apprehensive but it's a lot more laid back than
you'd think yeah we got this place under control no big deal what'd you think it was going to be
like well the lowest floor is home to some of the most dangerous guys here most of them have bounties
of at least a hundred million berries the rest are infamous in their own right bounty or no i was
pretty nervous when they told me i was assigned to the bottom floor and even more nervous when they told
me it was called the eternal hell but it's only really bad for the prisoners in other words i wouldn't
worry about it too much once they're here they'll never see the light of day well not until their
execution at least too bad because if you ask me death would be a heck of a lot easier than spending
the rest of your life in this hell hole you got a point there pardon the intrusion but the warden and
vice warden are on their way here with boa hancock we already got the heads up kind of makes you wonder
what she wants with fire fist ace though do you have a theory that's a good question man sure
sounds scary though the pirate princess and one of the most dangerous men in the world i don't like it
one bit speaking of dangerous men that other guy who's a warlord the one who rebelled against navy
headquarters he's got me on edge too strike me i have no regrets
that violent oath yeah captain i'm sorry lambs the brakes my body is fine my heart however
craves justice my heart wants war
king bae i can't die not here and not like this to hell with my title as a warlord i don't even want
it anymore if it means that i could stop this fight i would happily lay down my own life
no wonder we lost communication with level two those prisoners knocked a basilisk right into the
comm room those two were able to beat a basilisk where the hell are they anyway and what is going on
down there
wait hold on there they are i've got them you do really yes sir but now it seems there are
three of them there's what
nice job i think every wild beast on this floor is chasing us now okay guys we can't keep running like
this forever yeah and the longer we run the more people that are going to send after us because
this ain't exactly subtle you know still somehow that sounds better than getting eaten by these
things i'm too exhausted i can't keep this up
i don't have time for this crap
the big centipede just exploded into a bunch of little ones one centipede it was a bunch of poisonous
puzzle scorpions stacked on top of one another now there are more things chasing us
that's why i'm the best while those dumb animals
are following my footsteps we're free to make our break
but it didn't trip them for very long
damn these things by the way i heard the boss of beasts on level two looks like some sort of lion
are all of these things bosses of course they're not bosses these are clearly manticores
can't you see their human faces and if they catch us they'll chew until only bones remain
that's ours get the key in give me the key ignore them since they have human faces they can imitate
different people they've heard around the prison help me please it's too painful they're just
repeating things they've heard some of the prisoners say they have no idea what it means
what sure is creepy loincloth loincloth strawberry panties who the hell have they been listening to
around here beefsteak beefsteak beefsteak beefsteak
steak hey hey you you said you were gonna help us get through this place right of course i did and i
meant it we should join forces and break out of this prison together what do you say i told you i don't
want to break out want to know how to get down to level three huh i'm afraid you don't understand
the situation i assure you it only gets worse the deeper you go here's the scoop straw hat broke
into the prison to rescue his brother ace are you seriously telling me firefist ace is straw hat's
brother i never knew and you you broke into impel down to rescue him running out of time if someone
like firefist ace is being killed here then he would be all the way down in level five he wants to go
there no way help me out that's madness i wouldn't dare wait look i get that you don't want to join
us fine but how do we get there use the stairs you imbecile oh wait a second the stairs are all
connected from level one to level three i could use straw hat as bait for the beast guarding the stairs
and make my escape yes that's good what it's ingenious even no i'll stay let's go together
you can count on me's draw hat it's this way
oh crap you ran into something big
it's the guardian of the stairs the hellbeaks known as the sphinx
is that a lion or a grandpa
grandpa
oh my fries steak
more and cold
savory panties
noodle
what noodle
pork noodle
chinese noodles
the prisoners really talking about noodles that much
vegetable noodle
hot men
you mean me
this thing's tough
that's gotta be
that's face and he's going crazy about something
i knew it i just knew it we're gonna be stuck in this place forever
rice noodle hot pot noodle
kanto noodle
oh sanji used to make that man i sure miss my friends
wanton noodle
damn it he's strong and making me hungry
you know to be honest i have no interest in going down to the lower levels of this place
i'm right there with you on that one
now what do you say we form an alliance and break out of this dump
i'm so pleased to hear that you're a real escapee
now that that's settled let's begin the straw hat for dinner plan
my favorite plan
is
hey what are you two doing let's move
here he comes look out
now
what are you doing how's it a good idea to piss him off
that's not fair
why can't i go to a higher safer place too
so
i tricked you you ghastly abomination what you smashed was just a wax figure i created with my
waxwax power
though i admit they look much more convincing with miss golden wings coloring
but it was still enough to trick a foolish beast such as yourself
are you ready here we go
i think you can tell which one is the real me
okay
Let's try again.
Ha! That looks fun! Get him! Get him!
Not even close.
I don't even try!
You're bad at this.
Aw, man! Try there!
Just again!
Yeah! Get him!
He's playing with him. What the hell?
I know you're a risk-taker, kid,
but you're gonna laugh yourself into an early grave.
Not all! Not all! Not all! Not all! Not all!
Not all!
Seems like you're starting to get the hang of this!
Let the simpletons have their fun.
Now's my chance to make a break for it!
Hey, what's that rumbling and shaking all about?
Holy crap! Those three guys must really be pissing off the Sphinx!
Not all! Not all!
Not all!
What's happening?
I don't know, but I don't like it!
Level three to monitoring room!
We're hearing a lot of noise from upstairs!
Mr. Three, it's time to fly!
The perfect escape plan, huh?
This wasn't our plan! We're just running!
Works either way, I guess.
Hey, look! That must be the door that needs to the stairs!
I'll make a key out of wax!
Yes, this is the monitoring room!
Look, we still can't get in touch with level two!
So we have no idea what's going on down there!
No!
No, no, no! You stupid beast!
You've cracked the floor!
Now we're all gonna fall!
This is level three!
Oh, the ceiling is giving way!
The Sphinx is...
Oh, no!
Damn it all! We're falling to level three!
Noodle!
Oh, no!
Damn it all! We're falling to level three!
Noodle!
The government knows me as the pirate who hates other pirates.
An accurate assessment. Excluding your people.
Really? You? Hate pirates?
That must be a shock coming from me.
I used to visit Whitebeard's ship on a regular basis.
But because of my status with the government, I'd travel underwater to get there.
Even so, he and his crew were good friends to me.
Hmm. That's so. Well, I recall you almost killed me one time.
I suppose I can say the same thing about you.
But all that aside, I owe Whitebeard a great debt.
Fishman Island is now a peaceful haven once again.
And it's all thanks to that old man of yours.
As you know, pirates sailing along the Grand Line must pass through Fishman Island to reach the New World.
So not long after the dawn of the Great Pirate Era, the island was in trouble.
Numerous human pirates and Navy ships that were chasing after Whitebeard arrived there, wreaking havoc.
Countless fishmen and mermaids were kidnapped and sold as slaves.
And just when despair threatened to conquer our hearts, Whitebeard showed himself.
From this point forward, I claim this island as my territory.
A simple proclamation, a precious few words ensured that no one would lay a finger on Fishman Island again.
The power that Whitebeard commands is that great.
As long as I live, I will never forget that day.
Not just my homeland.
He protects other islands in much the same manner.
The government targets him because he is a pirate.
But they refuse to see the truth.
That is why I object.
If he happened to die, what would become of the sea?
Who would dare to welcome the chaos that would reign in his absence?
Who but a fool would dare to usher in such madness?
I want to stop this war, even if I must give up my life.
I wanted to rescue you, Ace.
But I failed.
Jinbei, please.
That's enough.
This is painful.
Even so, I haven't given up hope yet.
I believe that a miracle and our chance may come.
My, my, sounds like there's a lot of fun going on in the world.
This is a now or never opportunity to defeat Whitebeard.
Even locked down here, I can't help but feel a bit excited.
How dare you!
Oh, yeah?
You think you can take the old man?
Not just me.
Kill him!
They're gonna kill Whitebeard?
About time.
Take him out.
You gotta let me out of here.
I wanna be the one to kill him.
Let me out!
I wanna take a crack at him, too!
I'm gonna put an end to his era!
Yeah!
Fools!
Silence!
Jinbei, Ace, look.
Do you get it?
This world is full of dozens of second placers,
silver medalists who can never defeat Roger and Whitebeard,
All holding back their tears.
I swear, Stronghack, you're the biggest pain in the ass the world has ever seen!
Luffy and company descend to the Starvation Hell, where prisoners are forced to go without food or water, all the while enduring a torturous heat.
However, before they can escape this desert-like den of suffering, they fall into the Chief Guard's Trap.
On the next, One Piece, Chief Guard Saldath's Trap, Level 3, Starvation Hell, I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!